Finding Aid for Barbara Bach papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- State Government
  - Michigan Community Colleges Association (MCCA)
    - Office of the Governor
      - Commission on the Future of Higher Education 1984-1985 (Box 4)
      - Educational Summit Task Force 1984 (Box 4)
      - Labor-Management Conference 1986 (Box 4)
    - Governor's Office for Job Training
      - Staff Report 1984 (Box 4)
      - Newsletter 1986 (Box 4)
    - Cabinet Council on Jobs and Economic Development, Annual Report and Detroit News Article 1985, 1986 (Box 4)
    - Department of Commerce (MDOC)
      - Development Initiatives 1983-1984 (Box 4)
      - Employee Handbook 1985 (Box 4)
      - Newsletter on Economic Development
        - "Outlook '86" (May, June, July) 1986 (Box 4)
        - "Outlook '89 (July, September, December) 1989 (Box 4)
        - "Outlook '90 (January, July) 1990 (Box 4)
      - Office of New Enterprise Services (ONES), "Michigan Forum for ... Entrepreneurs," 1985, 1986 (Box 4)
    - Department of Education (MDOE)
      - Partnerships for Education Task Force 1986 (Box 4)
    - State Board for Public Community and Junior Colleges 1984 (Box 4)
    - MCC Presidents' Committee
      - June Meeting Agenda/Fiscal 1985-86 Appropriations 1985 (Box 4)
      - November Meeting Agenda/Advance Information Items 1985 (Box 4)
      - December Meeting Agenda/MCCA Committee Reports 1985 (Box 4)
    - Economic Development and Job Training (ED&JT) Network
      - Change of Network Reporting Relationship 1985 (Box 4)
      - Correspondence 1986 (Box 4)
      - Michigan Job Opportunity Bank (MJOB) 1985-1986 (Box 4)
      - Practitioner's Academy
        - Concept and Proposal 1985-1986 (Box 4)
        - Survey Questionnaire and Results 1986 (Box 4)
      - Discussion between MCCA and Network Offices 1985-1986 (Box 4)
      - Director's Final Activities Report 1986 (Box 4)
      - Director's Fiscal Year Budget
        - Summary 1985-1986 (Box 4)
        - Proposal 1986-1987 (Box 4)
      - Director Resignation 1986 (Box 4)
  - Michigan Tax Information Council (MTIC)
    - Conferences
      - First Annual 1983 (Box 4)
      - On Taxpayer Dissatisfaction 1984 (Box 4)
    - Program Plans and Correspondence 1983 (Box 4)
    - Program Summary, Budgets, Correspondence 1984 (Box 4)
    - Proposals, ca 1983 (Box 4)
    - Speaking Engagements 1983-1984 (Box 4)
    - Tax Limitation and the Voter's Choice Proposal 1984 (Box 4)
    - Newsletter, "Tax Talk"
      - Financing Public Schools Issue 1983 (Box 4)
      - 1983 (Box 4)
      - 1984-1987 (Box 4)
- Inventors' Council of Michigan 1983-1994 (INCOM)
  The Inventors' Council of Michigan (INCOM) series, 1983-1994 (3.3 linear ft.), documents Bach's role with an innovative organizational model created to encourage economic development through networking among individuals, corporations, and various types of service providers, including governmental resources. In order to reflect the era's widespread policy support for this approach, the series includes a sampling of records from associated groups such as the New Enterprise Forum (NEF), Industrial Technology Institute (ITI), and Metropolitan Center for High Technology (MCHT); it also includes newsletters edited by the former INCOM Director, Ed Zimmer, as well as conference agendas and selected published reference works.
  - Business Plan 1988 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence 1987-1993
    - Part 1 of 2 1987-1991 (Box 4)
    - Part 2 of 2 1992-1993 (Box 4)
  - Bylaws and Management Objective 1988 (Box 4)
  - Mission
    - Background and History 1990-1991 (Box 4)
    - Early Models for Encouraging Innovation, National Workshop at UM, MDOC Michigan Forum 1983, 1987 (Box 4)
    - Zimmer Foundation Proposal for Inventors Evaluation and Assistance Program 1987 (Box 4)
    - Larkin Group Prospectus and Flyer on the "Seven Deadly Sins of Entrepreneurship," 1988 (Box 4)
    - The "Product Tree" and "Inventor's Path to the Marketplace" Diagrams, ca 1987-1989 (Box 4)
    - State of Michigan Sponsored Events 1987 (Box 4)
    - Michigan Department of Commerce (MDOC)
      - Office of New Enterprise Services (ONES) Reviews 1988 (Box 4)
      - Special Edition of "Outlook" on Governor's Annual State of the State Address: Economic Development 1989 (Box 4)
    - "Case Statement" Overview, Educational Curriculum, News Coverage 1990-1991 (Box 4)
    - Nonprofit Organizations in Business News Sources 1990 (Box 4)
    - Situation Assessment by New Executive Director 1989 (Box 4)
    - Art Work and Evening Talk Slides, ca 1990 (Box 4)
    - Proposal Drafts, Strategic Plan, Role in Proposed UM IDD Michigan Technology Marketplace 1991 (Box 4)
  - Monthly Meetings (Box 4)
    - Sponsorship Program 1990 (Box 4)
    - Process and Table Sign-In 1990 (Box 4)
    - Agendas and Press Release 1991 (Box 4)
  - Sound Recordings of INCOM Speakers (Box 10)
    (Audio-cassette tapes)
    - Tom Thomas, Session I, March, 23 1990 (Box 10)
    - D. Weizman, Argo Technologies, Inc March 28, 1990 (Box 10)
    - Mark Young, Genesis Industries Group January 29, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Financial Statements 1987-1989 (Box 4)
  - Membership Marketing Plan 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Board of Directors
    - Membership 1988-1989 (Box 4)
    - Publicom Association Management Services Proposal 1988 (Box 4)
    - Meetings
      - Notes 1987 (Box 4)
      - Notes and Financial Status 1988 (Box 4)
      - Minutes, Zimmer Resignation 1989 (Box 4)
      - Alternatives for Operation and Announcement of Proposal to combine with MCHT 1989 (Box 4)
    - Leadership and Achievements 1990-1991 (Box 4)
  - Business Plan for Education, Curriculum-Centered 1991 (Box 4)
  - Photographs, ca 1990 (Box 5)
  - Membership Directories 1990-1992 (Box 5)
  - Metropolitan Center for High Technology (MCHT)
    - Society of Detroit Engineering (DE), "DE Technology" Journal, December Issue 1987 (Box 5)
    - "Classic Environment for High-Tech Growth" Brochure/Packet and Detroit Free Press Article 1987, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Newsletters, Press Release, Articles, and Events 1989-1990 (Box 5)
    - Affiliation Agreement 1989-1990 (Box 5)
    - Employee Conflict of Interest Agreements 1989 (Box 5)
    - Executive Director Reporting Relationship 1989-1990 (Box 5)
    - Fundraising, Request for Program Support 1991 (Box 5)
    - Board of Directors and Advisory Committee 1992-1993 (Box 5)
  - Inventors' Association of Metropolitan Detroit, Newsletter 1989 (Box 5)
  - Industrial Technology Institute (ITI)
    - Marketing Materials, ca 1988-1990 (Box 5)
    - Tornatzky, Louis G., and M. Fleischer, ITI, "The Processes of Technological Innovation," (Chapter 3), ca 1990 (Box 5)
    - Midwest Manufacturing Technology Center (MMTC) 1991-1992 (Box 5)
    - ITI Discussion March 12, 1987 (Box 10)
      (Audio-cassette tape)
  - Midwest Technology Information Center (Bay City), Newsletter, "New & Emerging Technology," 1987-1990 (scattered) (Box 5)
  - Business Enterprise Development Center (BEDC).
    - Walsh College and Oakland Community College Model 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Consulting Work
    - Budget, FY 1987-1988 including Student Interns, 1988 (Box 5)
    - Pilot Project
      - "The Planning and Pilot Operation of an Innovation Evaluation Program/State of Michigan," 1987 (Box 5)
      - "Establishing an Invention Evaluation and Inventor Assistance Program...," 1987 (Box 5)
      - Case Studies taken from Final Report 1987 (Box 5)
    - Solar Car Project
      - Eastern Michigan University (EMU), College of Technology, Flyer/Lecture Series-Innovative Technology, P. MacCready (GM Sunraycercar)/intro. by S. Ovshinsky May 18, 1988 (Box 5)
      - University of Michigan (UM)
        - Business Plan and Counseling. 1989-1990, 1993 (Box 5)
        - Thank You Letter and Car Photo 1990 (Box 5)
    - "Inventor Assistance and the Role of Michigan Business Centers as Service Providers," 1989 (Box 5)
    - Consulting Contracts-Small Business Development Center (SBDC) Project Planning and Program Development 1987-1989 (Box 5)
  - Inventor Assistance
    - Programs and Contacts 1988-1989 (Box 5)
    - Inventor Education Program, Summary Report 1989 (Box 5)
    - Exploring Consulting and Counseling Options 1989 (Box 5)
    - Counseling Model 1989 (Box 5)
    - Counseling Materials 1989-1990 (Box 5)
    - Counseling Request Examples, Small Business Administration (SBA) Form 1990 (Box 5)
    - Electronic Knock Control, John A. McDougal 1990-1991 (Box 5)
    - Aristoplay Ltd., Jan Barney Newman 1991 (Box 5)
    - Aristoplay, on WCAR Radio 1090 AM, September 15, 8-9 am, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Business Plan Reviews, Merrie Cain 1992 (Box 5)
    - Product Marketing Assistance, Joy Naylor 1992 (Box 5)
  - Inventor Survey
    - Preliminary Samples 1990 (Box 5)
    - Department of Energy Grant
      - Overview 1991-1992 (Box 5)
      - Response Samples, Case Study Narratives, ca 1991 (Box 5)
      - Presentation 1991 (Box 5)
      - Final Report, "A Profile of MI Independent Inventors...," 1991 (Box 5)
  - Inventors' Small Business Development Center (SBDC)
    - Announcement and Reporting 1988, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Ferris State University
      - Meeting 1987 (Box 5)
      - Manufacturing Resource and Productivity Center (MRPC)
        - Paper on "The Inventors Center of Michigan," 1988 (Box 5)
        - Invention Development Expertise and Services (IDEAS) 1989 (Box 5)
        - Newsletter, "Center-Vision: Technical Trends in Manufacturing," 1990 (Box 5)
    - John K. Greifer Analysis (Economics 501, Cross) and Udell Correspondence 1988 (Box 5)
    - Livesay, Rorke, Lux Research Article on Need for Education and Communication in the Innovation Process 1989 (Box 5)
    - Funding Plans 1988, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Center Closing and MI-SBDC update 1989 (Box 5)
  - Michigan Small Business Development Centers (MI-SBDC)
    - Contact Information 1987, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Leadership Retreat 1989 (Box 5)
    - Budget Projections 1988-1989 (Box 5)
    - Wayne State University (WSU)
      - Success Stories 1988-1989 and Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
      - Training Programs 1989 (Box 5)
  - National Development Council/Small Business Administration (SBA) (Box 5)
    - Economic Development Financing/504 Loan Program 1989
  - Marketing
    - Committee Members and Activities 1988-1989 (Box 5)
    - Innovation Example, Exxon Company USA 1988 (Box 5)
    - Public Relations Effectiveness, Publicom, Inc. 1989 (Box 5)
    - Inventors Association of St. Louis (IASL), Speaking Engagement and Newsletter 1988-1990 (Box 5)
  - Programs
    - Program Committee 1988-1989 (Box 5)
    - Economic Development Practitioners' Training Program 1988 (Box 5)
    - "Expo 1988" Second Annual Invention Exposition 1988 (Box 5)
    - "Expo 1990" Project Proposal 1989 (Box 5)
    - "Geode Award"
      - Reception and Inventions Display 1990 (Box 5)
      - Reception and Inventions Display, Second Annual 1991 (Box 5)
      - Award Nominees, Early Event Planning 1992 (Box 5)
      - Reception and INCOM Benefit
        - Event Planning, Management, Program Notes 1993 (Box 5)
        - Sponsorship and Budget 1993 (Box 5)
        - Award Nominees and Attendees 1993 (Box 5)
    - Idea Cars and Truck 1986 (includes photo), 1988, 1990 (Box 5)
    - Montgomery (RHM and Associates), "How to Offer Your Invention to Manufacturers," 1988 (Box 6)
    - "Turn Your Ideas into Dollars" Workshops (Box 6)
      - Inventor-Product Developer Textbook, R. Montgomery 1989 (Box 6)
      - Contract and Budget 1989 (Box 6)
      - Marketing 1989 (Box 6)
    - Touche Ross Workshops, Women in Business "Head Start" and Marketing Primer 1989 (Box 6)
    - University of Michigan (UM), School of Business Administration
      - Entrepreneurship Conferences 1989, 1990 (Box 6)
    - "Start-Up Clinics," 1991 (Box 6)
  - New Enterprise Forum (NEF)
    - Background and Purpose, Business Introductions at Monthly Meetings, Seminar Announcements 1988-1989 (Box 6)
    - Membership Lists, Fourth Annual Members Meeting and Monthly Forum Meeting (February) 1990 (Box 6)
    - Dan Davis Presentation Form, Letters, Journal Article 1990 (Box 6)
    - Monthly Meeting Materials (February and May) 1992 (Box 6)
    - Newsletters
      - NEF: April 1988, March 1989 (Box 6)
      - NEF: January-February, May-June October-November, 1990 (Box 6)
      - NEF: March 1991 Feb-May, Sept, Nov, 1992 January 1993 (Box 6)
      - Silicon Valley Entrepreneurs Club: July-August, 1989 (Box 6)
  - INCOM Newsletter
    - Prior Year Samples
      - February, June 1986 March, July, August 1987 May, Sept 1988 (Box 6)
    - Editor: Ed Zimmer
      - September-December 1988, January-April 1989 (Box 6)
    - Zimmer Foundation
      - 'Split' to Create New, "The Inventor-Entrepreneur Network"
        - May-June August-December 1989 (Box 6)
      - "The Inventor-Entrepreneur Network"
        - January-May, July November-December 1990 (Box 6)
        - April, July-August December 1991 (Box 6)
        - January-February April-October 1992 (Box 6)
      - "The Entrepreneur Network"
        - November-December 1992 (Box 6)
    - Metropolitan Center for High Technology (MCHT)
      - Redesign and Sponsorship 1990 (Box 6)
      - Content and Schedule 1990 (Box 6)
      - "The INCOM News" January-April; "INCOM News" October-November, 1990 (Box 6)
      - "INCOM Newsletter" (May-August / September) 1990 (Box 6)
      - "INCOM News" (April-May, July / August-November / December) 1991 (Box 6)
      - "INCOM" (January) 1992 (Box 6)
  - Conferences
    - Proposed National Conference on Creativity, Invention, and Technology Transfer; Other Topics 1987, 1990, 1993 (Box 6)
    - National Conference of Inventor Associations (2nd Annual) 1991 (Box 6)
    - Licensing
      - 1990 (Box 6)
      - 1991, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Handbook
    - Lessons from the Licensing Executives Society 1985-1988 (Box 6)
    - Early Plans for "Inventor's Handbook," 1988 (Box 6)
    - "Michigan Inventors' Handbook, Second Draft, Marvin Anderson," Sketch Draft 1988 (Box 6)
    - "A Handbook for the Beginning Inventor or Product Developer," Draft 1988-1989 (Box 6)
    - "Product Developers Handbook," Single-sided Draft with Annotations 1989 (Box 6)
    - "Product Developers Handbook," Two-sided Draft and Reviewer Comments 1989 (Box 6)
    - Production Specifications and Cost 1989 (Box 6)
    - Van Nostrand Reinhold Publishing Interest 1991-1992 (Box 6)
  - Michigan Industrial Developers Association (MIDA)
    - Announcements, Meeting Agendas, Newsletters 1984-1987, 1991 (Box 6)
    - Capitol Day Committee 1988-1989 Chamber of Commerce, 1987-1988 Legislative Directory, 1988 (Box 6)
    - Computer Technology Committee, Michigan Computer Aided Economic Development (MCAED) Program 1988-1989 (Box 6)
    - Treasurer
      - Membership Dues and Expense Reimbursement 1988-1989 (Box 6)
      - Budget and Financial Statements 1988-1989 (Box 6)
      - Citizens Research Council of Michigan Report (no. 292): Michigan Tax Climate 1989 (Box 6)
    - Vice-President 1989-1990 (Box 6)
    - Board and Membership Meetings 1988-1989 (Box 6)
    - Newsletter (December 1988) and Membership List 1988-1989 (Box 6)
    - Articles of Incorporation 1989 (Box 6)
  - Published Reference Works
    - Ann Arbor Chamber of Commerce, "The Entrepreneur's Handbook," Volume II 1984 (Box 6)
    - Auto in Michigan (AIM) Project 1988 (Box 6)
    - Gelman Sciences (Ann Arbor, Michigan), Annual Report 1992 (Box 6)
    - Independent Inventors--Who Are They? (Short articles including a reprint on first Colonial patent, 1902), ca 1989 (Box 6)
    - Lowe, Edward Main Street Journal, and White House Journal (page 3), "'Jobs' Are Not the Main Issue"), 1992 (Box 6)
    - Michigan Department of Commerce, "Guide to Starting a Business in Michigan," 1987 (Box 6)
    - Michigan Energy and Resource Research Association (MERRA), Technology Transfer, ca 1989 (Box 6)
    - Udell, Gerald G., "...the Idea Brokerage Function," Journal of the Patent Office Society 1975 (Box 6)
    - Warnings to Inventors 1988-1991 (scattered) (Box 6)
    - Washtenaw Development Council, Annual Report 1992 (Box 6)
    - Women Inventors 1989, 1992 (Box 6)
    - Zimmer, Ed, "Ideas vs. Inventions" and Other Topics 1988-1990 (Box 6)
  - Future of INCOM (Box 7)
    - Advisor Meetings on Strategic Planning 1991 (Box 7)
    - "Future of INCOM" Task Force Meetings 1992 (Box 7)
    - Financial Highlights 1990-1992 (Box 7)
    - Fundraising
      - "INCOM Fact Sheet," Sponsorship Presentation, ca 1990-1992 (Box 7)
      - Letters 1990-1992 (Box 7)
      - Hudson-Webber Foundation
        - Funding Request 1990, 1991 (Box 7)
        - Patent Search Photographs at Detroit Public Library, ca 1992 (Box 7)
      - Department of Energy Grant 1990 (Box 7)
      - Edward Lowe Foundation Correspondence 1991 (Box 7)
    - Membership Questionnaire and Responses 1991 (Box 7)
    - "Creative Options" for Commercialization, "Invention Development and Licensing" Article by Peter A. Hochstein 1992 (Box 7)
    - Response to "Bias against Large Corporations" Perception by Russell Monahan, NTN Technical Center 1991-1992 (Box 7)
    - Transition from Affiliation with MCHT/Detroit 1991-1992 (Box 7)
    - Volunteer Organization
      - Crain's Articles, Notes from Conversation with Ed Zimmer 1992 (Box 7)
      - Marketing Ideas 1992 (Box 7)
      - Newsletters, Monthly Meetings 1992 (Box 7)
      - Procedures 1992 (Box 7)
      - Project Management Services for Board of Directors and Executive Management Selection 1992 (Box 7)
      - Board and Meeting Schedule 1993-1994 (Box 7)
- Ann Arbor Community Service 1987-2008
  The Ann Arbor Community Service series, 1987-2008 (3 linear ft.), Bach's efforts on behalf of the City of Ann Arbor and as a fundraiser and or director for several Ann Arbor non-profit organizations. Through financial records, event announcements, and print-outs of emails, the series reflects organizational development and the shaping of a "corporate" culture more conducive to achieving the operational objectives of nonprofit organizations.
  - Ann Arbor Area 2000 Task Force on Huron River Development, 1987 (Box 7)
  - SAFE House Shelter Millage Ballot Proposal
    - Newspaper Articles 1992 (Box 7)
    - Campaign Manager
      - Campaign Agreement and Basic Information 1992 (Box 7)
      - Campaign Strategy 1992 (Box 7)
      - Campaign Logo and Coordination 1992 (Box 7)
      - Letters Requesting Support 1992 (Box 7)
      - Instructions to Flyer and Phone Volunteers 1992 (Box 7)
      - Election Day Instructions and Sample Ballot 1992 (Box 7)
    - Election Results
      - Detroit Free Press Article; Role of Women/Minorities 1992 (Box 7)
      - National Organization for Women (NOW), Ann Arbor-Washtenaw Chapter and "The Year of the Woman"
        - Newsletter and Talk at November Meeting 1992 (Box 7)
    - Time Magazine Cover Story on Women Abusers 1993 (Box 7)
  - City Council Vacancy
    - Resignation of 2nd Ward Councilmember Kirk Dodge 1993 (Box 7)
    - Appointment to City Council to Replace Dodge, 2nd Ward 1993 (Box 7)
  - City Council Member
    - Council Minutes and Business 1993 (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, Call-In, Other Council Agenda Items 1993 (Box 7)
    - Housing Commission/Housing Policy Board 1993 (Box 7)
    - Human Rights/Services 1993 (Box 7)
    - Downtown Development and Tax Increment Financing Plans 1982 (Box 7)
    - Downtown Development Authority (DDA) Meeting Agendas 1993 (Box 7)
    - Planning Commission Projects, Arbor Hills Planned Unit Development (PUD) 1993 (Box 7)
    - Parks and Wetlands 1993 (Box 7)
    - Fuller-Oakway Road Relocation Project 1993 (Box 7)
  - Campaign to Save Old Growth Oak Trees
    - Flyers, Articles, Phone List 1993 (Box 7)
    - Correspondence 1993 (Box 7)
    - Newspaper Stories on Veterans Administration (VA) Hospital Project 1993 (Box 7)
    - Other Area Woodland Ordinances 1993 (Box 7)
    - Natural Features Ordinance Committee 1993-1994 (Box 7)
  - Trees at Risk in Dhu Varren Road Improvement Plan 1993 (Box 7)
  - River Network
    - Correspondence 1994-1995 (Box 7)
    - Case Study and Local Proposals 1994 (Box 7)
    - Annual Report 1994 (Box 7)
    - Department of Natural Resources (DNR)/ Michigan's Natural Rivers Program and Stream Sites Information 1991-1993 (Box 7)
    - Michigan Year of the River 1995 (Box 7)
    - Michigan State University (MSU), Survey of Leaders: "What Do You Do?...What Are Your Needs?" 1995 (Box 7)
    - Newsletters
      - "River Voices," 1994-1995 (Box 7)
      - "Huron River Report," 1994, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Huron River News Clippings, Events. 1979, 1992, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Nichols Arboretum, Comments on Moving Historic House to Geddes Entrance 1995 (Box 8)
  - Housing Bureau for Seniors 1997 (Box 8)
  - Arbor Hospice 2004 (Box 8)
  - University of Michigan
    - Faculty Women's Club Chair, By-Laws 1999 (Box 8)
    - Museum of Art (UMMA) 2005 (Box 8)
  - Nonprofit Organizations
    - Nonprofit Enterprise at Work (NEW), Promotional Packet, ca 2003 (Box 8)
    - General and Fund-Raising Information 2000-2006 (Box 8)
  - Arts Alliance, "Community and Culture: Creating a Plan for Washtenaw County," 2007 (Box 8)
  - Child Care Network
    - History 1971-2002, 2002 (Box 8)
    - Annual Reports 1998-2001, 2003-2005 (Box 8)
    - Strategic Planning
      - Objectives and Vision Statement 1998 (Box 8)
      - Responsibility Matrix for Goals and Objectives 2001 (Box 8)
      - Business Week Article on Welfare Reform 2002 (Box 8)
    - Budget, with Comparison to Prior Year 2001 (Box 8)
    - Vision, Mission, Agency Services 2002 (Box 8)
    - Board of Directors
      - Questionnaire 2000-2001 Board, 2002 Retreat, 1999-2002 (Box 8)
      - President 2002 (Box 8)
      - Past President Development Role, Michigan Child Care Profile 2003-2004 (Box 8)
      - Board Development 2003-2005 (Box 8)
    - Enchanted Garden Party 2004 Benefit
      - Meeting Minutes and Email 2003-2004 (Box 8)
      - Fundraising, Budget, Proceeds 2003-2004 (Box 8)
      - Timeline and Event Planning Responsibilities 2004 (Box 8)
      - Promotional Materials for First Annual 2004 (Box 8)
    - Enchanted Garden Party Benefit 2005
      - Meeting Minutes 2004-2005 (Box 8)
      - Leadership Group and Host Committee 2005 (Box 8)
      - Fundraising 2005 (Box 8)
      - Timeline and Planning Manual 2005 (Box 8)
      - Promotional Materials 2005 (Box 8)
    - Enchanted Garden Party Benefit 2006 (Box 8)
    - Thirtieth (30th) Anniversary Celebration 2007 (Box 8)
  - Allen Creek Preschool
    - Invitation to Join Board 2000 (Box 8)
    - Graduated Intervention Program (GRIP) 1996 Annotated Comments and Questions, ca 2000 (Box 8)
    - Newsletter, Programs, Organization, Internal Audit Report 2000 (Box 8)
    - US Departments of Education/Health and Human Services, Early Childhood-Head Start Task Force Guide 2002 (Box 8)
    - Audited Financial Statements 2002-2003 (Box 8)
    - Parent Handbook and School Calendar 2004 (Box 8)
    - Organization Chart and By-Laws (adopted in December) 2004 (Box 8)
    - Strategic Planning (SP)
      - SP Report, RW Jacobs Consulting 2002 (Box 8)
      - Strategic Plan 2003-2008, 2003 (Box 8)
      - SP Core Committee (SPCC)
        - Information Gathering Packet #1 2003 (Box 8)
        - Scenario Development 2003 (Box 8)
      - SP Process, Town Meeting 2003 (Box 8)
      - Annotated "Final" Drafts 2003 (Box 8)
      - Greenhills School Plan and Website 2003 (Box 8)
    - Board of Directors
      - Strategic Plan
        - Website Summary of Board Status, Current Members 2004 (Box 8)
        - Approval of Plan by Current Board 2003 (Box 8)
        - Progress Review and Board Meeting Agendas 2005 (Box 8)
      - Meeting Agendas, Minutes, Email
        - 2001-2002 (Box 8)
        - 2002-2003 (Box 8)
        - 2003-2004 (Box 8)
        - 2005-2006 (Box 8)
        - 2006-2007 (Box 8)
      - Treasurer Duties 2002-2003 (Box 8)